University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the University Senate, 2001 November 18 - 2017 May 17; 1; 162 captures
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 December 10
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 7
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 7
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 14
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 14
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 28
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 28
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 4
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 4
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 11
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 11
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 25
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 25
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 4
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 4
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 18
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 18
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 20
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 25
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 March 25
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 8
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 8
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 15
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 15
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 23
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 29
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 29
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 6
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 6
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 13
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 13
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 20
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 20
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 27
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 27
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 3
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 3
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 17
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 July 17
    crawl: 165088
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2015-07-22T22:02:18Z
    end_date: 2015-07-22T21:28:19Z
    elapsed_ms: 448383534
    Crawl Types
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 432000
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 518483
    novel_count: 22064
    duplicate_count: 310947
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 185472
    downloaded_count: 333011
    download_failures: 280
    warc_revisit_count: 310940
    warc_url_count: 332912
    total_data_in_kbs: 92321075
    duplicate_bytes: 89386949991
    warc_compressed_bytes: 975896456
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.74
    kb_rate: 205.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 July 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 August 17
    crawl: 169175
    start_date: 2015-08-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2015-08-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-08-22T17:22:04Z
    end_date: 2015-08-22T16:57:37Z
    elapsed_ms: 432154021
    discovered_count: 580375
    novel_count: 18815
    duplicate_count: 281416
    queued_count: 280144
    downloaded_count: 300231
    download_failures: 232
    warc_revisit_count: 281408
    warc_url_count: 300140
    total_data_in_kbs: 104928074
    duplicate_bytes: 100253233235
    warc_compressed_bytes: 965534609
    doc_rate: 0.69
    kb_rate: 242.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 August 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 September 5
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 September 17
    crawl: 173356
    start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    original_start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-09-23T01:24:03Z
    end_date: 2015-09-23T00:16:53Z
    elapsed_ms: 458363239
    discovered_count: 367719
    novel_count: 26001
    duplicate_count: 206766
    queued_count: 134952
    downloaded_count: 232767
    download_failures: 237
    warc_revisit_count: 206761
    warc_url_count: 232678
    total_data_in_kbs: 101606587
    duplicate_bytes: 94029637527
    warc_compressed_bytes: 157865634
    doc_rate: 0.51
    kb_rate: 221.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 September 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 11
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
    crawl: 179047
    start_date: 2015-10-17T16:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-17T16:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-22T19:45:11Z
    end_date: 2015-10-22T19:02:36Z
    elapsed_ms: 439557452
    discovered_count: 390211
    novel_count: 36614
    duplicate_count: 202550
    queued_count: 151047
    downloaded_count: 239164
    download_failures: 276
    warc_revisit_count: 202548
    warc_url_count: 239075
    total_data_in_kbs: 61075441
    duplicate_bytes: 53769145120
    warc_compressed_bytes: 6127282356
    doc_rate: 0.54
    kb_rate: 138.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 November 17
    crawl: 183657
    start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-03T05:50:07Z
    end_date: 2015-11-30T19:18:26Z
    elapsed_ms: 432098049
    discovered_count: 415196
    novel_count: 17867
    duplicate_count: 229881
    queued_count: 167448
    downloaded_count: 247748
    download_failures: 242
    warc_revisit_count: 229876
    warc_url_count: 247648
    total_data_in_kbs: 61913750
    duplicate_bytes: 62091532709
    warc_compressed_bytes: 256259119
    doc_rate: 0.57
    kb_rate: 143.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 November 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 December 12
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 December 17
    crawl: 187970
    start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-22T21:57:26Z
    end_date: 2015-12-22T21:40:44Z
    elapsed_ms: 449129872
    discovered_count: 304232
    novel_count: 13877
    duplicate_count: 191764
    queued_count: 98591
    downloaded_count: 205641
    download_failures: 234
    warc_revisit_count: 191759
    warc_url_count: 205547
    total_data_in_kbs: 60257781
    duplicate_bytes: 60588343215
    warc_compressed_bytes: 34726906
    doc_rate: 0.46
    kb_rate: 134.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 December 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
    crawl: 191947
    start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-22T17:27:17Z
    end_date: 2016-01-22T16:56:58Z
    elapsed_ms: 432114027
    discovered_count: 573952
    novel_count: 20681
    duplicate_count: 273347
    queued_count: 279924
    downloaded_count: 294028
    download_failures: 181
    warc_revisit_count: 273342
    warc_url_count: 293928
    total_data_in_kbs: 63947333
    duplicate_bytes: 64312716410
    warc_compressed_bytes: 176478309
    doc_rate: 0.68
    kb_rate: 147.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 February 7
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 February 17
    crawl: 196723
    Crawl Rules
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ualbanysports.com (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for library.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for asrc.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for atmos.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cela.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for choose.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cs.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for csda.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cwig.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for events.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for hr.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for ibl.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for illiad.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for liblogs.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for listserv.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for m.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for omega.math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for mumford.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for nyjm.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for pdp.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for resnet.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rna.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for slsc.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uaems.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uapps.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for wiki.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    start_date: 2016-02-17T16:57:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-17T16:57:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-23T04:10:10Z
    end_date: 2016-02-22T23:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 454987781
    discovered_count: 7638127
    novel_count: 795824
    duplicate_count: 806868
    queued_count: 6035435
    downloaded_count: 1602692
    download_failures: 248
    warc_revisit_count: 806856
    warc_url_count: 1602561
    total_data_in_kbs: 226292461
    duplicate_bytes: 193554304269
    warc_compressed_bytes: 633147239
    doc_rate: 3.52
    kb_rate: 497.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 February 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 17
    crawl: 201840
    start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-22T18:02:10Z
    end_date: 2016-03-22T16:56:57Z
    elapsed_ms: 432107388
    discovered_count: 639552
    novel_count: 138564
    duplicate_count: 332568
    queued_count: 168420
    downloaded_count: 471132
    download_failures: 1411433
    warc_revisit_count: 332563
    warc_url_count: 471037
    total_data_in_kbs: 116820623
    duplicate_bytes: 113225737713
    warc_compressed_bytes: 765920585
    doc_rate: 1.09
    kb_rate: 270.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 April 17
    crawl: 207692
    start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-22T22:29:09Z
    end_date: 2016-04-22T18:00:08Z
    elapsed_ms: 435852385
    discovered_count: 7165982
    novel_count: 582992
    duplicate_count: 879835
    queued_count: 5703155
    downloaded_count: 1462827
    download_failures: 284
    warc_revisit_count: 879824
    warc_url_count: 1462700
    total_data_in_kbs: 227675763
    duplicate_bytes: 214936501775
    warc_compressed_bytes: 813502772
    doc_rate: 3.36
    kb_rate: 522.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 April 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 April 25
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
    crawl: 212937
    start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-24T10:38:52Z
    end_date: 2016-05-22T22:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 451503421
    discovered_count: 8685839
    novel_count: 568136
    duplicate_count: 1043240
    queued_count: 7074463
    downloaded_count: 1611376
    download_failures: 229
    warc_revisit_count: 1043205
    warc_url_count: 1611247
    total_data_in_kbs: 246906729
    duplicate_bytes: 230750229955
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2352496320
    doc_rate: 3.57
    kb_rate: 546.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 July 17
    crawl: 225859
    start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-22T22:52:35Z
    end_date: 2016-07-22T17:55:28Z
    elapsed_ms: 435383503
    discovered_count: 6792375
    novel_count: 212820
    duplicate_count: 1098346
    queued_count: 5481209
    downloaded_count: 1311166
    download_failures: 256
    warc_revisit_count: 1098317
    warc_url_count: 1311042
    total_data_in_kbs: 212249210
    duplicate_bytes: 207609316437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 675349961
    doc_rate: 3.01
    kb_rate: 487.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 July 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 July 29
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
    crawl: 231044
    Block host dev.library.albany.edu
    start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-23T01:20:50Z
    end_date: 2016-08-22T23:33:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 455703830
    discovered_count: 1189467
    novel_count: 184079
    duplicate_count: 736427
    queued_count: 268961
    downloaded_count: 920506
    download_failures: 267
    warc_revisit_count: 736404
    warc_url_count: 920384
    total_data_in_kbs: 202254345
    duplicate_bytes: 198029314926
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397770039
    doc_rate: 2.02
    kb_rate: 443.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 September 17
    crawl: 236726
    start_date: 2016-09-17T16:55:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-09-17T16:55:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-09-22T19:45:41Z
    end_date: 2016-09-22T17:03:18Z
    elapsed_ms: 432208662
    discovered_count: 1414002
    novel_count: 188377
    duplicate_count: 898376
    queued_count: 327249
    downloaded_count: 1086753
    download_failures: 287
    warc_revisit_count: 898345
    warc_url_count: 1086634
    total_data_in_kbs: 205611728
    duplicate_bytes: 200652210118
    warc_compressed_bytes: 309191153
    doc_rate: 2.51
    kb_rate: 475.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 September 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 September 30
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 October 17
    crawl: 243096
    start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-22T20:32:46Z
    end_date: 2016-10-22T17:07:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 432270469
    discovered_count: 1819420
    novel_count: 557303
    duplicate_count: 900445
    queued_count: 361672
    downloaded_count: 1457748
    download_failures: 296
    warc_revisit_count: 900407
    warc_url_count: 1457649
    total_data_in_kbs: 215568357
    duplicate_bytes: 201221539907
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1485925187
    doc_rate: 3.37
    kb_rate: 498.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 October 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 November 17
    crawl: 249672
    start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-22T23:26:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-22T18:15:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 436686458
    discovered_count: 6455397
    novel_count: 904107
    duplicate_count: 647491
    queued_count: 4903799
    downloaded_count: 1551598
    warc_revisit_count: 647445
    warc_url_count: 1551482
    total_data_in_kbs: 234676600
    duplicate_bytes: 166348006398
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22645478722
    doc_rate: 3.55
    kb_rate: 537.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 November 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
    crawl: 255339
    start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-22T23:02:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-22T17:39:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 434651176
    discovered_count: 5605147
    novel_count: 672626
    duplicate_count: 721586
    queued_count: 4210935
    downloaded_count: 1394212
    download_failures: 247
    warc_revisit_count: 721559
    warc_url_count: 1394095
    total_data_in_kbs: 173161585
    duplicate_bytes: 152072050167
    warc_compressed_bytes: 4226018506
    doc_rate: 3.21
    kb_rate: 398.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
    crawl: 261028
    start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-23T00:48:05Z
    end_date: 2017-01-22T19:31:33Z
    elapsed_ms: 440845477
    discovered_count: 6856243
    novel_count: 810250
    duplicate_count: 844972
    queued_count: 5201021
    downloaded_count: 1655222
    download_failures: 351
    warc_revisit_count: 844920
    warc_url_count: 1655090
    total_data_in_kbs: 260833049
    duplicate_bytes: 210669517964
    warc_compressed_bytes: 15598206209
    doc_rate: 3.75
    kb_rate: 591.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
    crawl: 267806
    start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T23:52:19Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T17:57:15Z
    elapsed_ms: 435595208
    discovered_count: 6181071
    novel_count: 757736
    duplicate_count: 820126
    queued_count: 4603209
    downloaded_count: 1577862
    download_failures: 339
    warc_revisit_count: 820090
    warc_url_count: 1577729
    total_data_in_kbs: 257873727
    duplicate_bytes: 232995142726
    warc_compressed_bytes: 5661819855
    doc_rate: 3.62
    kb_rate: 592.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
    crawl: 273971
    start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 436406787
    discovered_count: 7409222
    novel_count: 690900
    duplicate_count: 1257496
    queued_count: 5460826
    downloaded_count: 1948396
    download_failures: 359
    warc_revisit_count: 1257455
    warc_url_count: 1948270
    total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
    duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
    doc_rate: 4.46
    kb_rate: 611.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 April 17
    crawl: 291352
    start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-22T22:22:12Z
    end_date: 2017-04-22T17:55:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 435220728
    discovered_count: 8221578
    novel_count: 736180
    duplicate_count: 1311488
    queued_count: 6173910
    downloaded_count: 2047668
    download_failures: 335
    warc_revisit_count: 1311435
    warc_url_count: 2047538
    total_data_in_kbs: 284745035
    duplicate_bytes: 261915565851
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2411311996
    doc_rate: 4.7
    kb_rate: 654.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 April 17
  - University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
    crawl: 301465
    Host Rule Type C CONTAINS meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search? (last updated 2017-05-11)
    start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-23T00:29:43Z
    end_date: 2017-05-22T21:46:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 449440076
    discovered_count: 2923335
    novel_count: 388249
    duplicate_count: 1238165
    queued_count: 1296921
    downloaded_count: 1626414
    download_failures: 336
    warc_revisit_count: 1238113
    warc_url_count: 1626286
    total_data_in_kbs: 265327774
    duplicate_bytes: 251274786133
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3306915146
    kb_rate: 590.0
  - WARC file for University Senate - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
- Predecessor Bodies, 1915-1966; 2; 1.5 cubic ft.
  - Faculty Council, 1915-1966; 2.1; 1 cubic ft.
    Arrangement
    Arranged alphabetically and chronologically thereafter.
    Scope and Contents
    Includes minutes, committee reports, correspondence and by-laws of the Faculty Council. Bound with the minutes of the Faculty Council, 1944-47, are minutes of the Faculty-Administration Council. Committees of the Faculty Council included the Committee on Academic Freedom, the Community Liaison Committee, the Faculty Welfare and Obligations Committee, the Social Affairs Committee, the Elections Committee, and the Policies of Promotion, Tenure and Dismissal Committee (Faculty Handbook, 1962, p. 16). The functions of the Faculty Council and its committees were transferred to the Faculty Senate in 1966.
    - Bulletins of Faculty Council, 1961-1966 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 1)
    - By-Laws, 1961-1964 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 2)
    - By-Laws, 1961-1965 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 3)
    - Committee Membership, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 11)